https://www.greatriverfcu.org/privacy-policy/

MENUMENUMembershipAccounts
Saving
SavingsYouth/Teen AccountsShare CertificatesIRA/Money MarketHealth Savings
Checking
Personal CheckingBusiness CheckingCollege CheckingATM/Debit Cards
Lost/Stolen Cards & Checks
Identity TheftDisclosures
Loans
MortgageHome EquityAuto & Motorcycle LoansRecreational LoansPersonal LoansVisa Credit CardsStudent LoansBusiness LendingInsurancePayment Relief
Investmentse-Services
Digital BankingApply OnlineGo Live - Video ChatApple Android Samsung PayPhone Banking
About Us
About UsRate Your ExperienceGreat River Gives BackCareersContact UsCOVID-19 Updates
Login
Call (320) 252-5393
MENUMENUMembershipAccounts
Saving
SavingsYouth/Teen AccountsShare CertificatesIRA/Money MarketHealth Savings
Checking
Personal CheckingBusiness CheckingCollege CheckingATM/Debit Cards
Lost/Stolen Cards & Checks
Identity TheftDisclosures
Loans
MortgageHome EquityAuto & Motorcycle LoansRecreational LoansPersonal Loans
Business LendingVisa Credit CardsStudent LoansInsurancePayment Relief
Investe-Services
Digital BankingApply OnlineGo Live - Video ChatPhone Banking
Login
Username (How do I login?)
Mortgage Resources
Mortgage Timi (Test)
FACTS
WHAT DOES GREAT RIVER FEDERAL CREDIT UNION DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security number and account balances
Account transfers and credit history
Income and payment history
When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
How?
All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members’ personal information; the reasons Great River Federal Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does GRFCU share?
Can you limit sharing?
For our everyday business purposes– such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders or legal investigations, or to report to credit bureaus
Yes
No
For our marketing purposes– to offer our products and services to you
Yes
No
For joint marketing with other financial companies
Yes
No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes– information about your transactions and experiences
No
We don’t share
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes– information about your creditworthiness
No
We don’t share
For our affiliates to market to you
No
We don’t share
For non affiliates to market to you
No
We don’t share
Questions?  Call 1-888-211-5393 or go to www.greatriverfcu.org
What We Do
How does GRFCU protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does GRFCU collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
open an account or use your credit or debit card
provide employment information or apply for financing
make deposits or withdrawals from your account
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only-
Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes– information about your creditworthiness
Affiliates from using your information to market to you
Sharing for non affiliates to market to you
State law and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non financial companies.
Great River Federal Credit Union has NO affiliates.
Non affiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
Great River Federal Credit Union does not share with our non affiliates so they can market to you.
Joint Marketing
A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
Our joint marketing partners include insurance companies.
